Christopher Douglas Keller

Goodlettsville, TN 37072 615-971-9902 ckellermusic@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ christopher-keller-a9995b7/ GitHub: https://github.com/ ckellermusic/ CK Cyber Security

Profile

Cybersecurity devotee and experienced Nashville musician. A hard working learner dedicated to furthering skillsets in pentesting and network defense strategies familiar with the need to comfortably perfect a performance per request and guiding a band and clientele through the learning and doing process. A recent graduate of the Vanderbilt University Cybersecurity Bootcamp preparing for the Security+ certification

Projects

Elk Stack Project - https://github.com/ckellermusic/CK Cyber Security/tree/master/ Elk Stack Project

- Cloud monitoring system set up by configuring an ELK stack server

Red Vs Blue Project - https://github.com/ckellermusic/CK Cyber Security/tree/master/Red Vs Blue Project

- CTF exploiting a Capstone VM and using an ELK server to monitor attack through Kibana

Final Project -https://github.com/ckellermusic/CK Cyber Security/tree/master/Final Project - Implementing alarms and thresholds determined from the Red-Blue Project, assess two more vulnerable VMs and testing the new rules, and using Wireshark to analyze live malicious traffic on the wire

Skills

Languages: Bash, PowerShell

Operating System: Linux, Windows, OS X, Kali, Ubuntu

Tools: Metasploit, Wireshark, Splunk, Azure, Snort, Autopsy, Docker, Ansible, Kibana

Experience

Vocal Coach/owner, Chris Keller Vx Studios; NYC/Nashville – 2012-present

Independent, international commercial vocal coach for touring and studio artists

- Built and ran a successful independent vocal coaching studio working with clientele worldwide | chriskellervxstudios.com

Douglas Warren, Touring and Recording Artist; Nashville - 2009-2017

Independent recording, touring and Nashville Broadway artist

- Self managed music artist including self promotion, tour management, band management, and three studio produced EPs | <u>douglaswarrenmusic.com</u>

Education

Vanderbilt University Cybersecurity Boot Camp; Nashville, TN - Apr 2020-Oct 2020

Middle Tennessee State University; Murfreesboro, TN: B.M., Sep 2004-May 2007